<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml version="2.0">
  <category>
	<pattern>KNOWN STORY</pattern>
	<template>October. Another Saturday night out with friends, ten of us gathered in
the students union bar of the local red brick university to see the up
and coming Simple Minds. Five sets of couples strung out over soft
benches either side of rectangular tables that lined three sides of the
hall. While we waited for the band to take the stage, the usual buzz of
friendship played between us. Mercifully the music the D.J. played was
quieter than in Razor's Edge, so we could hear each other talk without
having to shout. 

I spotted Karl standing at the bar alone. It's hard to describe my
emotions after four months of no word from him and Milly. I had not
expected to see him again, thought my lust for his wife had destroyed
our friendship. It seems that the lure of danger Karen and I brought to
their world was a heady brew he could not forsake. A kind of joyous
terror swept over me. I scanned the room, my eyes seeking out Milly as
my mind became a shambles of uncertainty imaging what-the-fuck I would
say to her. 

Over the previous three months, there had been hardly a moment when
thoughts of her had not filled my mind, not a day I hadn't reviewed our
night together. And other times, going over how Karl and Milly had fled
without a word the next day, Karen and me waking to find their car gone,
the master bedroom empty, their passion-stained sheets heaped ready for
the maid, and my spent condom at the bedside where it fell the night before.

During the rest of our week away, Karen and I talked long into the
night, dissecting events over and over. We scrutinised the minutia,
hauled out the words that had passed between the four of us, reviewed
every look and shift of tone in our own and their voices. The aircraft
had exploded mid-flight. Now we would reassemble the fuselage and find
out the truth. I expected a verdict of death by misadventure, got only
one of pilot error—my culpable negligence. 

"You should have taken Milly to our bedroom," Karen told me when we sat
in the pub the day after our debacle. The place was quiet now, no
eavesdropping holidaymakers hanging on our every word.

"Why do you say that?" I asked.

"Then Karl would never have seen your bare arse pounding his darling-girl."

"You were watching us?"

"Not much else for us do after his two minutes of rutting."

"That quick, eh?"

"Two is generous."

"Poor you."

"Yes! Poor me."

"Serves you right for sucking his cock as soon as you got on to the bed
with him."

"You and Milly would never have happened if I hadn't."

"And did you watch too."

She nodded.

"So how do you think I did?" 

"Jesus, Luca. Do you want me to give you marks out of ten!"

"It's just that things didn't go quite as I'd expected."

"Listen, darling, if Karl had given me half the attention you gave
Milly, I'd have been a happy little bunny indeed."

Karen and I grew closer that week, sharing things we had always promised
to share but never had. That was the time she told me how she and
Malcolm had met up and gone to the pub together when she'd told me she
was going around to her mum's. Just chatting, she told me. But
afterward, Malcolm would drive her up to Stanchurch Woods and get her to
suck his cock in the front seat of his Escort Mexico. 

And I told her about Wendy, a girl I had once worked with who I ran into
unexpectedly one afternoon while travelling on a bus that time my motor
was in the garage. I'd taken her back to our house while Karen was at
work and fucked her three times over as many hours. Later I walked her
to the bus stop, saw her off on the one-three-seven to Hanging Cross. 

I realise some readers may never understand how these mutual confessions
brought us closer together. We had married too young, had not played the
field. Our licence to shag others was our getting it out of our system,
belatedly sowing our wild oats. But underneath the facade of
permissiveness, Karen and I were soul mates. We still are forty years
later. Our wayward sexuality rested on the founding stone of love. And
because of that bedrock, our relationship accommodated the weight of
more than just each other.

So when I saw Karl that night in the students union bar, Karen and I
were in a good place, in fact, a better place than ever before. I went
to him without hesitation. "Hi stranger," I said, shaking his hand. He
was my friend, and apart from my being infatuated with his wife, I loved
the guy, valued his friendship more than most.

He smiled and returned my handshake, quite warmly so that I knew we are
okay again. We chatted as if nothing had happened — that I'd never
fucked his wife of barely eighteen months.

"Where is she?" I asked. It took real resolve to field the question,
fearing what had happened between the four of us has ruined them and
that they were no longer together. 

And then her voice from behind me. Me turning to see.

 "Hi, Luca. We knew you'd show for Simple Minds, so we thought we'd
better come and check up on you — make sure you and Karen are behaving
yourselves." 

She was standing with another couple, who I recognised as her older
sister Chrissy and her husband, Steve. We had met only once before at a
party the previous year. I nodded, and they said hi. There was a look in
Chrissy's eyes whose nature I found hard to determine. It was as if my
actuality in the world secretly amused her. 

And then Karen was by my side, and it was like nothing had happened
between the four of us — except that it had, and I could not forget that
it had. Forty years afterward, I still cannot forget that it had. I
still obsess about it, is the reason I write about it now, daring myself
to set it down for all the world to read. 

I tried to read Milly, studied her expressions as we chatted hoping
there were vestiges, remnants of feelings for me still present. But what
I saw deflated me. I was no more than the bloke I ever was, a friend of
her husband: Luca, good for a laugh, the guy into all that crazy shit.

The jeans and adolescent counter-culture props had gone, she was all
silver earrings, rings and bracelets. She, wore a real silk blouse, long
suede skirt, and brown leather knee-length boots. But her hair was the
same as before. Baby-fine strands of moonlight falling to her shoulders.
Previously she had smoked only occasionally, but that night a cigarette
was rarely out of her hand, coming and going between darkly glossed lips
that framed only the most fleeting of smiles.

We insisted they join us at our table — Chrissy and Steve too. And the
four of them followed us back to the tables where our friends were
sitting, Karen coaxing Gemma to budge-up to make room for Milly, my two
ex-lovers ushered side by side for a while. They hardly knew each other,
but soon Milly's warm breath was among Gemma's thick dark waves saying
words I could not hope to hear. I wondered what secrets she was
whispering, what hooks she might dangle to get Gemma to confess more
than she should. 

It occurred to me even back then how Milly had Gemma at a disadvantage —
you know, what her knowing all about Gemma and Malcolm, those weeks when
Malcolm and I would fuck each other's wives. But poor Gemma. She had no
idea about what had gone down between Karen, Milly, Karl and me.

And then later, Gemma off dancing with others, I was talking to Malcolm
while Milly and Karen sat together across from us, also talking. I later
learned all about their talk, how it was a night of sharing, sincerity,
confession and contrition. I watched how their conversation ebbed and
flowed while imagining Milly's warm breath on Karen's cheeks, just as I
had known it on mine six months before. Except this was not Razor's
Edge; the volume of the music did not warrant such intimacy. At least
not until the band came on stage. But just then their words were still a
mystery to me. Weeks would go by before Karen's telling would make them
unravel. 

Watching them talking so intimately kinda turned me on. It was a
spectacle that demanded male voyeurism, bordered on indecency. I
expected the pair to begin kissing at any moment. When I turned to my
side, I saw Malcolm staring too, his expression as if entranced. 

"That blonde girl," he said when he saw I was looking. "Milly, isn't it?"

"What about her?" I asked. 

"I keep expecting her to start snogging your misses." 

"Would that be such a bad thing?" I asked in my best blokeish way and
then laughed as blokes should.

"Fucking criminal, mate — if I weren't lying between the pair of them,
that is?" he said. And I thought of Karl, and how Karen had sucked his
cock while Milly had kissed him and begged him to let me fuck her.

"You wish," I said.

"Too fucking right, mate. Just look at them knockers will you!"

I didn't like to say I'd done more than look.

But when Milly and Karen went off to dance with the others, Malcolm
began banging on about some deal he was involved in, one he was sure
would make his and Gemma's fortune. I was losing the will to live, so
when he became distracted by Maggy my sister-in-law on the seat to on
the other side of him I made my escape, went over to talk to Chrissy and
Steve sitting further along the row opposite. I hardly knew them but
they looked interesting. Especially after the way Chrissy had looked at
me earlier. And the fact Chrissy was Milly's big sister made it a must.
Though she was not big at all, she was petite, her hair
Pre-Raphaelite-ginger to the shoulders, all cork-screw curls.

I sat down next to her and began feeling my way with words, trying to
break the ice. I asked about their little boy, Bradley, who was just
three years old back then. And of course, what woman doesn't like to
talk about their kids. Steve just nodded as his wife began to tell me
about her son's new nursery in exquisitely excruciating detail — so much
so that I began to wish I hadn't asked. 

After only five minutes, Steve went off to get drinks, and it was as if
she had just picked a Get Out Of Jail Free card from the Community Chest. 

 "How was your holiday?" she asked, "Aberdaron, wasn't it? Shame how
Karl became unwell and had to come home."

"Yeah, real bummer. It spoilt the whole week," I said. "Karen and I had
been hoping to spend lots more time with them."

 I was wondering what she knew, tried to think of ways to fish for just
how much Milly might have told her.

"Are you and Milly close?" I asked.

"We weren't when we were kids, what with me being six years older than
her. But lately, we've been talking a lot. You know, sorting out her shit."

"What sort of shit?"

"Secret shit."

"What kind of secret shit?"

"It wouldn't be secret if I told you," she said while smiling, her eyes
unwavering.

I was about to come right out with it and ask her what Milly had been
saying about me when a song started up that made me think of Milly. I
had played it non stop during the months after I'd fucked her—Bowie's
/Rock 'n' Roll with Me./

Chrissy said, "I love this track." And I said that I did too. 

She stood up and said, "WIll you dance with me, Luca?" She did not wait
for my reply, reached down for my hand and pulled me to my feet. 

"What about Steve?" I asked. 

"We're only going to dance, aren't we? She saw my uncertainty, smiled
and said. "Steve has diversions of his own," and she smiled again,
pinned me with come to bed eyes.

To get to the aisle, we brushed past the knees of the others like at the
cinema. Karen and Milly were back in their seats talking, and as we
passed them Milly stood up and whispered something to Chrissy. I looked
down at Karen, and she met my self-satisfied smile with an exasperated
glance. I shrugged my shoulders, smiled sheepishly. It was a smile that
said it's not my fault chicks throw themselves at my feet.

Chrissy led me to the far side of the dance floor, to a spot where no
one from our group could see us. Before dancing, I asked her, "What did
Milly whisper to you?"

"She said I had to watch out for you. Now, why would she say something
like that?"

"You tell me, she's your sister."

We began dancing facing each other but not yet touching.
Chrissy'smovements were slow and sensual, exquisitely fluid. The music
had captured her thoughts, and she closed her eyes and let her mind
become lost to emotions that only music has the key. When I had walked
with her to the dancefloor, I'd kept telling myself that/ this girl is
just asking for it/. But when I saw how she danced, lost to some inner
rapture, I become less sure. 

And so we danced facing each other as my mind travelled retrograde back
to the time I had first come-on to Milly. I had been so cock-sure of
myself that night, convinced she would be my play-thing. But I was
changed because of happened between Milly and me, and as I reached out
to take her older sister in my arms I anticipated only her scorn,  

I touched Chrissy's arm just above the elbow, and she opened her eyes
looking quite startled as if I had just woken her. For a fleeting
instant there was uncertainty in her expression. And then she seemed to
remember who I was, smiled and said, "Yeah, why not." 

She stepped towards me and allowed me to take her into my arms. Her
dress was loose-fitting cotton, and when I placed one hand in the small
of her back, the other between her shoulder blades, the material went
slipping about under my touch, my palms skating her skin beneath. The
garment, concealed little of her body's nature as I let my hands slide
here and there enjoying her softness and curves, her warmth and lithe
feminine plasticity. She looked up at me as we danced, her eyes full of
amused delight. I could not believe she was Milly's sister, her sexual
assurance a stark counterpoint to that girl's gauche uncertainty. 

Her arms had encircled me, and now one hand rested way below my
shoulders, the other at the base of my skull holding my head in place
while she went up on tiptoe to kiss me, pressing her body so tightly
against me that the convexity of her small breasts cushioned my ribs.
She had complete fluidity, was utterly at ease in her body, shockingly
confident of her sexual appeal. 

While we kissed, I sensed how her torso, legs, and arms all conceded to
me so that I feared she might relinquish her own living substance. Her
body swayed to the music, softly pressing against me, her groin unctuous
against my hips as if her flesh was liquifying. So much so that I feared
she might empty away and that I would find myself alone on the
dancefloor cradling only her rags.

But for all the visceral sensuality of our encounter, in the end,
Kissing Chrissy was throw-away. It was how I had expected to kiss Milly;
casually, with irony. Because I could. And although Chrissy had far more
sex appeal than Milly, was a wonderfully sensual kisser, to me she was
just another girl, one like any number of others I had kissed in the
past. In contrast, when I had kissed Milly, her grateful biddability had
taken my breath away, stoked my masculine determination. Perhaps that
was it: Milly back then had felt ill-defined, the boundaries of her
personhood still nascent. It was if she had taken on the guise of the
person I needed her to be.

And so for a few hurrying minutes, I kissed Chrissy Catterall (nee
Saunderson), Milly's older sister. For me, at that moment, it was the
Saunderson family's reparation for the months of emotional torment that
their youngest daughter had brought down upon me. Now Chrissy had paid
war damages, brought about the restitution of my pride.

Later that night, I was standing at the bar when I saw Milly and Karen
head for the ladies. I followed them out and waited in the corridor.
They emerged together arm in arm, giggling like adolescents.

"I want to speak to Milly," I told Karen.

"I don't think that's a good idea," she replied. Then turning to Milly,
"You don't have to speak to him, you know. Not if you don't want to."

"No, it's okay, Karen. He should know — hear it from me."

"Hear what,?" I asked.

"Okay, I'll leave you to it," Karen said.

When Karen had gone, I told Milly, "I just wanted to say I'm sorry if
I've caused any upset?"

"I'm not upset."

"What about Karl. How does he feel about you and me now?" 

"Luca, there is no you and me. There'll never be any you and me. I've
promised Karl there will never be anything between us — not that there
ever was."

Her words cut deep. My voice might have cracked when I said, "I wish I
could have made it more special for us." Immediately I regretted my words. 

"We'd all drunk too much," she said. "I'm as much to blame as anyone."

She saw how I was suffering, and so added. "Listen, Luca. If I were a
single girl, I would have come back for more the next night — and the
night after that. But I'm not, am I? I'm married to Karl and want it to
stay that way. Do you understand?" She looked at me so intently, her
eyes insistent, impressing on me with the gravity of her feeling on the
matter. 

Clutching at straws, I asked: "Can I kiss you one last time."

"Oh, God! You just don't get it, do you?" And with that she turned and
walked away.

Months went by. Karen and I would drive over to our home town every
weekend to be with our friends. But it was months before I saw Chrissy
again. 

Little by little, Karl began to see that Milly had no feelings for me. I
for my part was behaving myself. I put a brave face on, tried not to
look at her. My mind harnessed by constant thoughts of Milly became a
team of horses galloping to the edge of psychosis. It wasn't as if I
wanted to abandon Karen, leave her for Milly. A person can love two
people at once, I told myself. Loving one person didn't in any way
lessen the love for the other. But I understand myself now: what I
wanted from Milly was for her to fall in love with me, for her to adore
me unconditionally. God!, what a narcissistic, selfish bastard I once was.

Milly would write to Karen at least once a week, tell her about her and
Karl's days. We had yet to get a landline installed in our home, and
there was no email back then. Letters from friends were a real treat,
and I still have them in a box in the attic. Not just those from Milly
and Karl, but those from many other friends.

Late November. For two weeks we had to skip our usual weekends out with
friends. Karen was away in Lancaster on some open university module
essential to her work. The Thursday before she went we argued. She said
I should snap out of whatever it was that was plaguing me, that my
self-pity as getting boring. She let me know quite pointedly that while
she was away that she was going to find someone to fuck her. But that's
another story.

The following week we received a letter from Karl and Milly saying how
the previous Saturday they'd gone to a club together and then separated
for the night. They had pretended to be single, flirted and danced with
strangers. The thought that Karl was now allowing Milly free reign with
other blokes while I was a no go area filled me with simmering
resentment. I was his friend, and yet I was off-limits. Throughout that
week, the ache of my jealousy was crippling.

"So Karl doesn't mind his wife messing around with others as long as
it's not me?" I said to Karen when the retort from the bombshell had
settled. It was a Thursday night just after dinner.

"So the penny has finally dropped," she said. "Perhaps we can get back
to having a little fun. You know, the kind that doesn't entail the four
of us getting our kit off."

"Has she spoken to you about me?" I asked.

"Not recently. Milly's more interested in me these days."

"What do you mean?"

"Once, you would have loved what I'm going to tell you, but I'm not so
sure anymore."

"So tell me then."

"A bit back, Milly was asking me stuff."

"Stuff about me?"

"You're obsessed, Luca. You two are history. No, she was asking stuff
about me — you know, asking what turns me on." 

"That must have been one long conversation."

"Yes, it was," she said flatly. 

"So what did you tell her?"

"Among other things, about how I love to have the soles of my feet
massaged while I'm having my pussy licked?" She waited for my
affirmation, and only when I nodded did she continue. "She said she
wouldn't mind helping me out in that department."

"But Karl told me that Milly hates to suck cock."

"It's not a cock she'll be sucking."

If I'd been standing up, my legs would have failed me. In an instant, my
cock was hard in my jeans. "And what did you say?"

"I said she was welcome to anytime that suited her."

"And what did she say?"

"That she'd arrange it, find a way to get some time away from Karl."

"So is it sorted?"

"Is it heck! I can't seer her getting time away from Karl any time soon,
can you?"

"Surely he won't mind you and Milly together?"

"I'm tainted by association, so she doesn't want him to know. Any other
woman, Karl would be okay with."

I imagined Karen naked on her back, her knees drawn way back, the slash
and curls of her pussy a puddle of need as Milly kneeled before her,
eager to do the deed, pushing her hair to one side and leaning forward
to begin.

 Karen and I made love until the early hours that night.

Two weeks before Christmas, Milly and Karl had us over for the weekend,
a futon in their spare room after Razor's Edge. By the time we got back
to their house, I was the worse for drink. I crashed out after one last
joint on a bean bag in their lounge. Seeing the state of me, Karl
thought it safe to go to bed, that Karen was no threat to his
darling-girl. HE left the pair sitting together on the sofa talking —
always fucking talking.

Karen and Milly as two conspirators, the hush of their voices like a
dream as I drifted in and out of wakefulness. Their chatter subsiding,
growing intimate, then lost beneath the music of Nick Drake. Even with
Milly so close — so close that I could reach out and touch her leg — I
could hardly keep myself awake. But when the music stopped, the silence
that inundated the room snapped me from my dozing. For a moment I
thought Karen had gone to bed and left me where I fell, just as she
would when back at home if I had fallen asleep on the couch.

It took me a moment to realise that the two of them were tottering on
the edge of a precipice, that they were about to plummet into a chasm of
sexual intimacy. Each had turned to face the other, and now there was
excited anticipation in the looks they exchanged. It was like poker,
each daring the other to reveal her hand.

 Then the end of suspense. Karen reached out brushed aside strands of
Milly's hair before leaning in and kissing her cheek softly, letting her
mouth linger momentarily before making its way to her chin. In the
silence of the room, I could hear each peck of her lips against Milly's
perfect skin. Then her tongue went sliding along the sharp cut of her
jawline, on to her ear lobes, and then down to her neck where I lost
sight of it among moonbeams of hair. The slop of her nuzzling was
unmistakable in the dead air of the room. I could only imagine Karen's
hungry mouth: her fiendish canines and lapping tongue.

 But I could see Milly's face clear enough, how she inhaled and exhaled
as if steadying herself, her eyes growing dreamy before she closed them
as she unburdened herself of all qualms, any thought of consequences.
Her features became serene, her hand absently stroking Karen's dark hair
as her mouth roamed her neck and throat at will.

And then they were lost in kissing, mouth to mouth, tongue chasing
tongue. I could hear both girls breathing, their passion for each other
ungovernable. It was as if they shared a growing panic that this moment
might pass and would never come again. And so they rushed to take from
each other all they could, their lust about to skip a species to become
more than either could contain.

 Karen's fingers at work on the buttons of Milly's blouse, undoing the
top four, giving her hand room to slip inside her bra. I watched as it
moved and disappeared to settle beneath the satin fabric, stirring from
time to time like a small living thing sequestered away sheltering from
cold and fear but still unable to find rest. While I watched, I
remembered the wonder of holding Milly's large and firm breasts, and I
grew harder than I thought possible, so much so that I slipped my hand
inside the pocket of my jeans and held my cock tightly to stop it
bursting out of its skin.

Milly's hand went to Karen's knee before moving up the inside of her
thigh, pushing the hem of her skirt before it as I travelled. I'd like
to tell you I saw her fingers kneading Karen's pussy through her sheer
black tight and panties, but I can't. At some point, her hand
disappeared in the bunched fabric of the skirt and became lost to view.
But I did see how Karen parted her legs to facilitate Milly's
exploration, heard how she gasped when the girl's fingers found their mark.

The sound of movement upstairs. A door opening, a cistern flushing. Karl
on the landing calling for his wife. Milly, in a moment of panic, on her
feet and straightening her top. She did not look back at Karen, rushed
from the room without a word.

I went and sat beside my wife on the sofa, in the space vacated by Milly.

"Shame, she had to rush off like that," I said. "things were just
getting interesting." I could smell Milly on her, in the ar all about
her. It was that shop-girl-reek of Smitty by Coty. Karen's friend Gemma
had worn the same cheap scent the night I'd fingered her pussy three
years before. 

Karen's voice, little more than a gasp. "What a fucking little bitch to
just go off like that." Then she pulled me to her, saying, "Just Kiss
me, Luca. Kiss me — kiss me just like you did her."

We began to kiss, Karen almost out of her mind with need. Her tongue
filled my mouth, its clamour and sweep telling me that only the
completion of orgasm would cure her of such a virulent fever. I slipped
a hand under the waist of her skirt, her tights and panties too. The
binding clamp of the unfastened fabric on my forearm hindered my rhythm,
and so as we kissed she fumbled with the side fastening of her skirt,
allowing my hand deeper, enabling it to reach the dead point of her craving.

Karen gasped when my fingers found her clit. I could have gasped too;
how its swelling betrayed her need. I imagined its ache, how it must
torment her. Neither had I anticipated her wetness. It was a shock to
find that such a brief encounter with another female had soaked her so
thoroughly.

Then my imagination became Karen's imagination, and I made my lips
Milly's lips, my fingers Milly's fingers. I wanted to steal from Karen
the inner turmoil that kissing Milly had stoked in her and make it my
own. My Johhny Ramone fingers became such fabulous bringers of bliss.
Her torso buckled when her orgasm hit and she gripped me like a woman
drowning, sucked the air from my lungs as we continued to kiss. It was a
detonation that shook her to her core. And like a breaker when surfing,
it had picked her up and then dropped her and submerged her, sending her
tumbling down into the collapsing barrel of its ecstasy, making her
writhe where she slouched half-propped beneath me. Her cries of pleasure
were beyond understanding, were guttural and protracted, full of
self-beratement for allowing such a brief encounter with Milly to
unhinge her so thoroughly. 

I clamped my mouth over hers, a perfect seal to stifle her cries. In
mere seconds, with my fingers and tongue, I had taken away all of her
simmering need, all of her lid-rattling irrational cravings for that
silly teenage girl. I had lifted it from her, carried it away and set it
aside on the back burner next to my own brewing pot of limerence and
delusion.

We went upstairs to the guest bedroom, where the futon and sheets
awaited us, undressed with feverish abandon and then slipped beneath the
duvet where we fucked without restraint. I did not bother to muffle
Karen when she began calling out to God, howling cries of ecstatic
affirmation. No! I was thoughtful, had decided Milly should hear just
how much I could please a woman.

I'll finish that at a late time babe.
</template>
</category>  

</aiml>